{
    "id": "92a07c2c82aa416fa36a7647aff5b516",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She was angry …………………… him for stealing her ideas.",
            "description": "Angry with/at a person for doing something.",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She was angry …………………….. everyone.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "That voice is familiar ………………………… me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "with",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "A cock and bull story is ……………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "an unbelievable story",
                "an interesting story",
                "a false story"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "To move heaven and earth is to ………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "pray to god",
                "work hard",
                "be happy"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "To lead up the garden path is to ………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "help",
                "guide",
                "cheat"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The juice in the cans …………………………. very delicious.",
            "description": "Here the subject is the singular noun juice.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I wish I ……………………… a bird.",
            "description": "Were is common after I wish to talk about unrealistic situations.",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "were",
                "am"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The accused behaved as if he ………………………….. mad.",
            "description": "Was is also possible here however, were is more common than was in an unreal comparison. ",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "was",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "If I were you, I ………………………. to that proposal.",
            "description": "In the second conditional, use a simple past tense in the if-clause and would + first form of the verb in the main clause.",
            "answers": [
                "will not agree",
                "would not agree",
                "would not have agreed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "His mentor and benefactor …………………….. his professor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "An assembly of churchgoers is a ……………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "convocation",
                "congregation",
                "conflagration"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}